I'm not sure where your education came
from, but they lied to you. I hope some
of y'all are acting. I really do. I knew
I was gonna be surrounded by ignorance,
but damn. Let's go. And my points are
just as valid as yours, even though you
got a pocket square and a Church of
Christ uh pin on your chest. Y'all just
want to be seen. I don't need to be
seen.
>> That's why you're dressed like a poison
dark space that is tricking you into
fell in.
You need to think about me as your mama.
Do not talk to me in that fashion.
>> You need to think of me like your mama.
How entitled can you be? Let me ask you
this. Can you identify, and I'm not
talking about talking heads. I'm not
talking about people who are just in the
space where they they revolve around
political commentary.
>> Can you identify a major black celebrity
who's conservative?
>> I heard Denzel Washington.
>> Uh, no. He's he's he's voted Democrat.
He's a Christian. And he encourages
accountability, but doesn't fully
connect the dots. And by the way, I from
everything that I've seen and heard like
Denzel Washington, we probably would
disagree on some issues politically. Uh
do another question for you. Do you
think there's ever going to be a point
where the scales tip? Because we saw it
with Hispanic votes. We saw it with
Jenzi. We've never seen it to a
significant degree with black votes in
America. And we have more black
representatives or commentators uh than
ever. You know, back when we were
growing up, you pretty much had Thomas
Soul and kind of Larry Elder. Um there
was like Alan Keys, Herman King.
Alfonso. Rachel was an early and OG. I'd
recommend go checking him out on
YouTube. He was one of the first people
there. But now you have a ton of people.
the Blexit never really materialized. Do
you think that it'll ever happen?
comment
and uh
I I I also understand why it's so um
it's so tipped uh towards one side uh as
far as politically with black people
because if you look or listen to
anything in media um you will only see
black celebrities assuming that you must
be you must be unless you're a traitor
uh liberal if you're
We are voting for the right to choose
what happens to our own bodies.
>> We are
>> Don't black I choose you
>> ourselves from this precipice of danger.
>> I misspelled respect
>> and a lot of y'all
>> I thought I had a case
>> corrected me
>> and a hashtag.
Now, I want y'all to help me correct
President Trump to teach him what it
means.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, please. Nice
haircut.
>> Big loud Texas welcome to the next
president of the United States, Vice
President
Har.
>> You think that this guy has done stuff
for black people?
All I got to say is crack is whack. I'm
not trying to be funny.
>> Well, mission accomplished. nothing has
never done nothing for black folks.
>> Thank you for the
>> It's a double negative. That means he's
done something.
>> I know you guys are excited to see her.
I didn't know you guys would be excited
to see me, too. But uh
>> yeah, I got to go disappear to what I
call training camp for a few weeks. Come
back with a bald spot and 10 new pounds
of muscle. Now
uh this brings us to uh the uh I keep
want to say outnumbered, the surrounded,
which for those of you who are
unfamiliar, it's basically change my
mind with a vote timer. Um, it is, it
really is.
>> And this is one black radical. This is
uh an actress, Amanda Seals, uh, versus
20 black um, conservatives. Now, here's
the thing. I We're going to get into
some of the claims versus the reality.
Um, but this is important to to note.
It's a technique that's used a lot and
I've encountered it in change my mind
quite a bit. Right. Change my mind was
just sit down, establish the premise,
which they refer to as a prompt, and
anyone can sit down and, you know,
change your mind. Okay? You've seen
people do this where what they do is the
in-betweens. If they know their argument
doesn't really hold any water, they try
and taint it with things like, you know,
gh, you're unreasonable, or gh, I can't
believe these people must be paid actors
or gh. They try, if their argument
doesn't hold water, they try and tip
those scales on. It's performance art.
So, as bad as you thought this was going
to be with Amanda Seals, it's much
worse.
>> I'm not sure where your education came
from, but they lied to you. I hope some
of y'all are acting. I really do. See, I
knew I was going to be surrounded by
ignorance. But damn, let's go. And my
points are just as valid as yours, even
though you got a pocket square and a
Church of Christ uh pin on your chest.
>> It's not a Church of Christ. It's
>> whatever. It's a cross. Same difference.
You got an American flag and you think
you know something cuz you a cop and
ultimately not a cop. It's a It's AAB
all day over here. So, let me make that
clear, dude. I'm being direct to you,
but you're literally speaking this and
you're not going to do that with me
either. So, you're stating your point.
Y'all just want to be seen. I don't need
to be seen. That's why you're dressed
like a poison dart frog. face that is
tricking you into like she fell in four
buckets of paint. I have not had you
know
>> first of all you're a lightkinned woman
so are you and you're doing great
colorism. Yes. And so colorism really
does serve us. God this is scary. You
need to think about me as your mama. Do
not talk to me in that fashion.
>> So let's check that now.
>> See and this is what happens too.
Sometimes referred to tone policing but
she's telling some you need to do this.
Now, I don't mean it's it's very
reasonable to require someone if you are
offering them respect to be respectful.
Like, hey, I didn't and I've done this.
Hey, you know, I let you finish.
>> You got to let me finish. Or
occasionally I'll go, you know what? I'm
going to finish uh my thought as though
you're an adult capable of giving me the
same respect I've given you. But that's
not what she's doing. You need to think
of me like, yo, mama. How entitled can
you be? You don't get to tell someone
what to think or how they should view
you. Here's how someone's going to view
you. Usually, it's usually going to be
based on your actions.
And in this case, your words, your
stupid, stupid words. So, seals, just to
give you an idea, was at the center of
quite a few uh controversies herself.
For example, defending Jesse Smlet,
quote, "Even if it was a hoax,"
>> what?
>> Yeah. This is someone who just if black
people can do no wrong, even if it was a
hoax and cost taxpayer dollars and and
the city and even if it did stir racial
division and hatred, you know, another
hoax, too, like Michael Brown, hands up,
don't shoot. Jesse Small, it's funny,
Black Lives Matter, the terrorism, the
billions of dollars in damage, that was
also a hoax. So, she was also kicked out
of a black Emmy party. She got into a
feud with a black sorority and she
claimed that she was autistic without
ever actually being diagnosed, which is
funny. But hey, it's not just black
white. That's feminism to the letter.
Just claim victim status and you assume
you win the argument. But that doesn't
fly here. It's time for claim truth.
>> Can we go back claiming autism as a a
tool in an argument?
>> That's real harded, sir. Sure.
>> Yeah. It's a it's a it's a thing that a
lot of people do.
>> The only person who never will is Al
Sharpton who spells respect with two
K's.
>> Respect.
>> I misspelled respect. It's cra That was
actually very revealing cuz to me I just
thought it's the way he speaks. No, in
his mind he's going R E S P E K K K K K
K K K K K K K K K K K K K K K K. That is
what it means to me.
>> Yeah, there's a whole song.
>> I don't know. I I don't think I would
ever get to the point in argument where
I'm like, but I'm
>> Yeah. Well, you don't need to say
>> I don't think you said an argument. I
think she was just claiming it.
>> She's claiming it. Yeah. But why anyway?
>> Because it's a status symbol these days.
>> It's a victim.
>> It is. It's like
>> it's like one of these things. I'm a
marginalized group. I'm I'm I'm not only
am I black, but I'm also a woman. And
not only that, but I'm on the lowest end
possible of beinged. Yeah.
>> No, no, no. I don't I get it. But then
you try to put yourself out there as
somebody who can articulate the points
of why reparations are a thing. Like
you've basically just under Oh, so I
don't need to listen to you.
>> No, no, no. I understand. You're being
logical. That's your problem. is if you
take away victim status, right?
>> If you completely remove it, in other
words, if you don't go wait, black,
white, okay, well, hold on a second. Um,
white woman, black guy, what, uh, trans,
okay, disabled. If you take all of that
away,
>> you actually have to um rest on the the
validity of your arguments,
>> your actual thoughts, your opinions. So
if you take all of the identity politics
away, it just comes down to actions,
performance,
arguments, claims, we can't have that
and we certainly don't have that in the
public school system. So the first claim
uh that's made is
systemic and this has been addressed and
changed my mind well over half a decade
ago. Actually, systemic racism, by the
way, challenge is still out there of one
example today in the 21st century.
Systemic racism is real, says the
self-dagnosed.
>> Ultimately, systemic racism exists in
our institutions on a government level,
in our institutions, whether it's
prisons or schools, and it is undeniable
because they are actively trying to
reinstate it right now.
>> Okay. So, the truth, it's hard to deal
with claims that make no sense. I don't
know what she means by trying to
reinstate it. And I watched the whole
thing and it still doesn't make sense.
uh blacks are completely proportionally
represented in Congress, right, in
government. Okay, about 14%. And as far
as prison now, again, her premise, but
again, she's she's on the spectrum
according to her, is just black people
are being put there because they're
black. Black people in this country,
despite making up 12 to 13% of the
population, commit over half of all the
violent crimes. And then if you look at
way systemic discrimination, okay, well,
we know that Asians and white people
have been discriminated against in
colleges, for example. have to have
higher GPA, better SAT scores, and still
can't get in. Whereas black students who
are woefully underqualified in some
cases, they do. They do get in. DEI
exists.
It And here's the thing, too. When she
goes on to talk about reparations, they
act as though those things have never
taken place. DEI is repar affirmative
action is reparations. Model cities
program is reparations. EBT, SNAP, the
baby mama that was created by these are
reparations. section 8 housing, more
money into public school. These are
reparations that have been paid to the
tune of trillions of dollars and have
made nothing better. Now, she may say,
"Those aren't the reparations we want,
but those are the reparations that exist
because it's what their party and what
their community, the black community,
have demanded. They petitioned. They got
these reparations
and it didn't work." The answer, if you
ask them, so when is it enough is always
more. Here's the next claim. that she
makes.
>> And this is a tough one. I don't even
know. It's like grabbing a bar of soap.
Uh,
>> which kind of soap? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Done. Soap.
>> Harriet Tubman was uh actually aided by
white supremacy something.
>> I refuse to embrace a victim mentality
because that's not what our grandparents
and Harriet Tubman and those people
fought for. They fought for Harriet
Tubman's name in vain. Baby, please.
>> They said the Lord's name in vain. the
Lord's name.
>> Harriet Tubman was literally
literally
saving her family and others from
slavery.
>> Yeah. You know who helped her? White
people.
>> You know who helped her?
>> They were on the Underground Railroad.
Come on in.
>> No. You know who helped her?
>> Come on in.
>> God. And
>> people who benefit from white supremacy.
>> What?
>> That guy had answers.
>> Yeah, he did.
>> He did. He did. Uh, okay. So, the truth
to this one the I uh uh Okay, so
here's my understanding of her of her
again self-dagnosed uh autistic argument
is that um white people helped Harriet
Tubman, but they could only help her
because they were beneficiaries of white
supremacy.
>> Therefore, white supremacy helped
Harriet Tubman. Okay, so you don't want
allies.
Get it done with 12% of the population.
I would help, but I benefit from white
supremacy. Everyone in this room, by the
way, you're procluded from helping
because you've benefited from white
supremacy. Tell that to the the Quaker
church who helped Harriet Tubman.
>> Yeah. Tell it to Massachusetts Governor,
uh, John Andrew.
>> Mhm.
>> Tell it to the multiple whites who
helped with the Underground Railroad
specifically, just to be clear. No, no,
no. You guys all have to stop because
you've benefited from white supremacy.
Oh, so the slaves should do it on their
own. This is a way of removing any and
all credit for the good deeds that white
people have committed in the name of I
know this is inconvenient. Modern
Christendom. Yeah. I don't understand
what this point like. If you didn't have
white people, nobody would know about
Harriet Tubman. You know why? She
wouldn't have made it. We wouldn't let
you write books about it and you
wouldn't be free.
>> Mhm.
>> So maybe just saying thank you. You know
who else has a bene who's benefited from
white supremacy? Um, the wealthiest
celebrities on earth. There you go.
Beyonce, NJ-Z, the top box office draws
of the the uh Will Smiths of the world,
the Denzel Washingtons of the world, the
three most recognizable faces on earth
in the '90s, Michael Jordan, Michael
Jackson. Kind of, that's a half one.
Mike Tyson, because white, you know who
else? Barack Obama, president of the
United States. I know that one's pretty
crazy.
>> That's rough. also white people the ones
who've given you the platform to speak
these kinds of asinine opinions uh in a
show like surrounded not outnumbered the
next claim
>> that she makes that blacks absolutely do
need reparations and she's going to make
an airtight case
>> now let me land the plane we're talking
about reparations and what you're doing
is actually get this conversation off
the facts and the fact is reparations
are just and necessary because on a
basic level, black people built this
country and this country continues to
thrive off of the labor that black
people put into this country. And it
would behoove you, young man, to really
understand the way that your ancestors
put blood, sweat, and tears into this
nation that is still living off of those
blood, sweat, and tears.
>> Okay? And I'll open this up to you guys,
but here's the truth. All right? Couple
of things. I just addressed this, right?
When you talk about EBT, SNAP, section 8
housing, more money to public schools,
when you talk about affirmative action,
DEI, these are all forms of reparations.
To be clear, I think at some point she
says repatriations. I'm not entirely
sure. She kind of delineates between the
two.
>> Remunerations.
>> Is that what she says? Yeah,
renumerations. Sorry. Reumerations. Um,
okay. And she'll say, well, that's not
what now we're asking for money. Okay,
great. But those things exist because
your community and the Democrat party
said that those were required.
Okay. Those were required. That's the
rep to the tune of trillions of dollars.
Why is that not enough? And by the way,
why do reparations need to be paid to a
15-year-old blackout? What kind of
reparations does Jesse Smalllet deserve?
And is it wiped out by what he costs the
good good taxpaying citizens of Chicago?
I know you say you should defend him
anyway because it's just a hoax. Oh,
that's right. Now I'm getting it. The
answer is always more money, please.
More money, please. You asked for
reparations.
You may not like them now. It's what you
asked for. You got them.
You're saying it's not enough. Now
you're on your own. The other thing is,
by the way, I'm so tired of this. All
references available, link in the
descriptions. Um,
blacks built this country. No, they
didn't. No, they didn't. in comparison
to the labor in this country and
certainly in comparison to the
businesses created and the innovations
uh in this country and and yes manual
labor especially if you look at the
industrial revolution you look at these
great booms that took place in this
country it is not because of black
people they took part in it but not any
greater part than anyone else 75% by the
way of southerners didn't own any slaves
whatsoever states like California never
had any slaves to be clear and while
we're talking about this. The vast
majority of slaves, anywhere from 90% to
96%, I think the high number 96% comes
from Cornell West. Uh they were sold
into slavery by West African slave
traders. Also, if you want to go buy
yourself a slave today, you can still do
it in plenty of African nations. You're
going to be dealing with a black person,
though, so don't be surprised. Here's
the next part of this is um slavery too
actually can be argued through the
metrics. It held the country back.
The free north outperformed the south
while they still had slaves in every way
you could measure economically.
The cotton industry exploded after
slavery ended. Innovations like the
cotton gin that came from the areas of
the country that didn't have slavery. So
this is something and it's something
that used to it's used to guilt white
people. You wouldn't have this country
if not for black people. Okay. Well,
black pe Africans who were sold by their
African brothers. Hey, they're still
there in countries in Africa. What does
that look like?
What's the difference?
You have Africans in both.
They're slaves in both. Slavery is
wrong. To be clear, just like Hitler
bad. Africans in both. Slavery and slave
owners alike in both. Pick a country.
Any country. The African continent.
United States. What's the difference?
who built the country.
>> One of the most infuriating things that
she does is she makes these claims as
though they're self-evident, right? She
just says, "Yes, systemic racism
exists." We were trying to think about,
okay, well, how do you combat that
without going down 50 rabbit holes?
Okay, we'll go with what she said.
Government, prisons, and schools. Okay,
we can't prove that because we just
disprove that. Reparations are
absolutely just and needed. Okay, well,
how do you prove that? Who gets it?
Right. These people, we built this
country. Therefore, she goes to the next
point as though that foundational
statement is true. I just wish she would
say something with some kind of factual
backing. Quote a study, even if I don't
agree with it, just something, a stat.
Give me a number to go after. In fact,
when the guy brought up statistics about
black-on-black crime, she goes, "Stats
lie all the time, honey. If you're going
to make your argument about stats, you
already lost."
>> Yeah.
>> It's exactly what she did. It's like,
"Oh, so I will never ever You're just a
racist person." Yeah. That's really what
we're dealing with. a racist person who
hates this country. Fantastic. Here's an
offer from me. Not this show, from me
personally. I will write you a check
right now to pay to have you move to
Africa. Let me ask
>> because apparently you don't like it
here.
>> Yeah. Let me ask you.
>> I don't want to be I don't want to be an
oppressor.
>> No. No. None of us do. Let me ask you
this. If you went to Harriet Tubman back
in time and said, "Hey, look,
>> you can you can tomorrow slavery is
done. You don't have to do this railroad
stuff, okay? It's done. It's over.
>> This railroad stuff.
>> Everyone will be free. Everyone will be
free.
>> All this malarkey,
>> but that's it. It's a fresh start. The
only way we know how to do this, Miss
Tubman, you've inspired us, is to to to
break these chains. Slavery is done, but
we just got to get a fresh start. We
can't keep looking to the past. It's
over. Everyone's free.
>> Do you of course she would take that
deal. And if she saw a seal, she would
tell her to get a haircut and sew up the
holes in her jeans. Here's a bonus claim
that she makes that uh just sort of
shows that she's an actual racist if you
didn't know that by her defending Jesse
Smlet because of his blackness. Uh the
claim here is that the Chinese aren't
actual minorities or something like
black people. I don't know.
>> For example, you have the uh Chinese
Exclusion Act of 1882. We prevented
Chinese people from getting citizenship
and even entering the country. We
discriminate against them and basically
put them under apartheid even here in
the United States. Yet they have the
highest median household income. How is
that possible? How come they don't
complain and feel entitled consistently
to bend for reparations and for this
when they are killing each other 90% of
the time, which is the rate that black
people kill each other according to the
FBI?
>> Oh, young Matt. One,
comparing Chinese people who are
immigrants that made a choice to come to
the United States and comparing the
continued effort of black people to
ground themselves in a nation that
continues to make impediments for them
to show and live and exist in their true
citizenship is a false equivalency. I
don't believe that happens at all. What?
What? No one here is in
>> Are you acting right now? Do you believe
I'm telling the truth?
>> There's a way to try and discredit the
person. Now, before I get to the truth,
let me just tell you this. I'm also I
think that you're placating by saying
black people kill black people in record
numbers, cuz that's You know what I'm
actually really concerned with? I'm also
really concerned with the fact that
black people kill white people in this
country in record numbers.
It's not just your community's problem.
>> No. And we have a right to an opinion
because we are several times more likely
to be assaulted, to be mugged, to be
robbed, or to be killed by a black
person as a white American than by a
white American. Yep. The numbers are
even higher because of the proximity
effect of black people living around
other black people. But let's be honest
about this. We're concerned that we're
more likely to be the victim of crime.
And you can't blame it on there not
being enough affirmative action. Anyone
want to Anyone agree with that? I'm
tired of going, "Oh, the black-on-black
crime, they're the biggest." No. Yeah,
sure. They're the biggest threat to the
black community. I'm very concerned with
them being a threat, that community to
my white children. Got it.
>> That's a great point because in this the
the longer version of the video, you
know, other people brought that up and
it is a real concern, but she her her
response was uh well, how many how many
black people do you see in your
neighborhood on a day-to-day basis? A
lot. How many white people do you see in
your neighborhood on a day-to-day basis?
Some. Well, well then that's not that's
why that's you're not you're not in
danger from white because you don't see
white people.
>> Yeah. Yeah. The only problem is if you
look at the armed robbery, you look at
the burglaries, you look at the violent
crime taking place in the white
neighborhoods, you know, the next town
over, you still see the same stats. In
other words, these gangs of largely
black people, they travel.
>> And we have a problem with it.
>> Round get around. They get around.
>> The Browns Browns Browns browns. They
get around.
But here's the truth. Uh, the Chinese in
the United States, it's not a false
equivalency. They weren't even
considered citizens until 1943. 1870
>> is when the 15th Amendment gave black
men the right to vote. To be clear,
1920, the 19th Amendment, some would say
a mistake, granted black women the right
to vote. Not because they're black, all
women. And uh, today, yes, the median
income for Chinese Americans is 82,000
versus 54,000 for black Americans. So
they've been discriminated against far
more recently in a way that would
negatively affect their income. They
bounce back and by the way richer than
the average German just to be clear like
the Chinese do really well.
>> You keep saying it wrong.
>> The Chinese pronounced Chinese admonish
me.
>> Yes. Admonish him alone.
>> I don't want to be ethnosentric.
>> Do it alone.
>> Chinese go down with a ship.
>> And by the way, these metrics show you
they Chinese. They know dumb. They are
doing very well.
>> They know the maths. So, I don't know
why it's plural in other countries, but
it is. Hey, so let's let's just concede
the argument that she makes right now. I
just want to concede every single point,
right? I know we don't want to do that,
but let's just concede every single
thing you say about white people in this
country, white supremacists and Harriet
Tubman, systemic racism everywhere.
You're right. You owed every single
dollar in my bank account. Do you think
that's going to happen? And is that the
best advice for all of your constituents
to try to get that? or let's just say
that they're an oppressive system that
they can never get out of, which is kind
of what you're claiming in the first
place. Wouldn't it be better to do what
the other cultures have done and just
try to make the very best of it that you
possibly can and try to fix that instead
of just complaining and shaking your
fist at the sky and saying every bad
thing that happens to you is because of
the white man keeping you down. That's
what works. You don't care about your
community. Yeah. You care about having a
grievance. You care about having an
excuse for failure,
>> right? instead of saying, "Hey, we need
more fathers in the home in this
community. Hey, we need less violence in
this community. Hey, we need better
education in this community." And guess
what? Those people aren't going to give
it to us. Fine. We're going to do it
ourselves.
>> Yeah.
>> I tell you who who really wants
reparations.
>> Chrysler.
>> Oh, I thought you said I thought you
said preparations. I was thinking it's
big H.
>> No, no,
>> reparations. But I'm not going to say
it.
>> And by the way, bring up a bonus uh for
uh those who are members of Rumble
Premium for Mud Club. By the way, if
you're not, click that button below.
We'll go on for another hour. Uh it's
$99 annual. You get everything ad free.
You get 100% more show including the
Friday show and uh it's the only thing
that keeps the lights on or try it for
$9.99 a month. Where they talked about
with her
>> uh black culture and they talked about
hip-hop and the things that were
glorified and she said, "Well, who's the
one feeding black people that? Who's the
one?" So if if they're force-feeding you
junk food and in other words it's white
people who are largely responsible for
the mass consumption in the black
community and rejection by the way of
any and all other forms of media as it
relates to gangster culture as it
relates to decadence and hedenism that
you see. Um I would have loved to ask
her what's on your playlist.
>> Yeah.
>> What do you think's on Jesse Smlet's
playlist? Why have you been duped
>> by the evil white man? I'm guessing Jew,
right? Why have you been duped?
>> It is our fault.
>> We amended the bucket and the mop.
>> Yes. Yes. Yeah. It's which is after
which she modeled her hairdo.
>> Oh, you're still here. And you're still
watching this on YouTube. You've
probably noticed something is missing by
now. I'm not here. That's because the
Live Daily Show is now streaming
exclusively on Rumble weekdays at 11:00
a.m. Eastern. Tune in there where
nothing is censored.